# Harold Seo

haroldseo.github.io/portfolio/ - linkedin.com/in/haroldseo/ - github.com/haroldseo Los Angeles, CA - (213) 327-6225 - harold.seo.612@gmail.com

# Summary:

I'm a Web Developer working in React, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, Node.js, and Ruby on Rails. Prior to becoming a web developer, I worked as an Accounts Receivable Specialist at Promesa USA. My responsibilities included tracking orders, confirming transactions/payments, and maintaining records. Currently, I'm working on freelance project, building a WordPress site for The Beacon Church.

# Technical Skills:

- Languages: JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, Ruby
- Frameworks & Libraries: React, jQuery, Express, Node.js, Rails, Bootstrap
- Databases: MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- Other Technologies: WordPress, Git and Github, SASS, Heroku, AWS, JSON Web Tokens, AJAX, PHP, Passport.js, Socket.io, Google Maps API, Twilio API, API.AI

# **Projects:**

### 1. ChatApp

A web application, for users to communicate through chat. Users have the option of chatting in a global chatroom, private chatrooms, or to a ChatBot. This application was built using React, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Bootstrap, JWT, Socket.io, and API.AI.

#### 2. Dozer

A web application that alerts the user through call or text when they are approaching their destination. This application was built using Node.js, Express, AJAX, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Passport.js, Bootstrap, MongoDB, Twilio API, and Google Maps API.

#### 3. But First, Coffee

A full-stack application for users to find local coffee shops and review them. This application was built using Ruby on Rails, HTML5, CSS3, and Bootstrap.

# 4. Tag, You're It

A two-player game of tag. This game was built using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and jQuery.

# Experience:

Freelance Developer, The Beacon Church, July 2018

Promesa USA, Accounts Receivable Specialist, Jan 2017 - Jul 2017

BBCN Bank, Accounts Payable Specialist, Jun 2015 - Aug 2015

# **Education:**

# **General Assembly**

Web Development Immersive, 2017

### California State University Northridge

Bachelor of Science (BS), Kinesiology and Exercise Science, 2010 - 2016